The Fruit of Evolution 2:
Before I Knew It, My Life Had It Made
The True Fruit of Evolution
Creep
Fatty
True Fruit of Evolution
Before I Knew It, My Life Had It Made
I want 1 + I Love You
I want you to hold me
no matter how I look
Is that selfish of me?
An "I love you today, as well"
kiss in the morning
A "You're cute" kiss in the afternoon
A "Let's meet in our dreams"
kiss in the evening
Imagining those things
makes my heart feel like it's bursting
I want to say it, I want to
say it, I want to say it,
But will you laugh
when you look at me?
(Sparkle sparkle sparkle My Love)
But, but, but my dear,
The fact that I love you
is as colorful as my body is big
and ever evolving
See
I want 1 + I Love You
Love
No one's asking
who you are?